♪ We light up the night, yeah ♪
♪ We light up the night ♪
[cheering]
[cheering, screaming]
[all chanting] Mary! Mary!
Mary! Mary! Mary!
[birds chirping]
[gentle knocking on door]
-Hello?
-Should I knock quietly?
[laughing] Are you alive?
We brought you a little hair of the dog.
-Oh, my God, no.
-If that doesn't work,
I brought you a barf bag. [laughing]
I take option B.
Option B?
-[Mary chuckles]
-Okay.
I could not, if my life depended on it,
drink any more.
I'll put it here, maybe later.
Chrishell, how the hell
do you look so good?
Well, it was your bachelorette party,
so I think you went a little harder.
-[Mary] Yeah.
-Which is good.
A little too hard, I think.
[Mary] I'm like...
I'm regretting... a lot.
[Heather] I feel like shit.
I might throw up in the planter.
-I'm serious.
-Please, don't throw up.
[sighing] Okay.
[Christine] Last night was pretty...
-interesting.
-[Heather laughing]
Did you have fun?
What do you think about everything?
Yeah, I had fun.
I wasn't like, "Wah!"
But I was drinking out of a penis straw.
I think, like, the room was fun.
-We had good laughs.
-It was fun. Yeah.
We're all okay around each other,
-but there's little issues.
-[sighs]
I just had a little bit of anxiety
even going to the hotel,
-to the room.
-You and Davina both, because...
Davina didn't want to be around Mary.
You don't really wanna be around Amanza.
-It's like-- I totally get it.
-Yeah...
I don't wanna be around Mary,
Mary doesn't wanna be around me.
Let's be honest.
So what did I miss, because I...
It was so much fun.
There was a little bit of drama.
-[Amanza] Was there? I wanna know.
-I can't remember. Wait, I remember...
Oh, good! She doesn't remember.
-Never mind.
-No, what happened?
Remember when you and Heather
were catching me up on the fact
that she was engaged?
-We were at the 44 million dollar house.
-[gasps]
I do remember this.
That I was saying there was
an overlap or something.
Did you use that word?
'Cause she's really stuck on whether
or not you used this certain word.
And I was like, "I don't know."
-She said, "overlap."
-I don't remember.
-Overlap of what?
-There was a comment about overlap.
And I was thinking, like,
"Wow, those bitches were, like,
talking shit about my relationship."
I was sitting next to them
and I could hear them talking about it.
So I was like, "Let me just squash it
so that this doesn't go any further."
Chrishell was chiming in,
"What are you guys talking about?"
"Oh, we're talking about relationships."
People talking bad about my relationship,
your relationship.
I could tell she was like,
-"Oh, shit."
-Oh... Yeah.
I don't know exactly.
I could overhear her saying
you thought maybe he was
with somebody when they met.
-Oh, got it.
-Or something. I don't know.
Well, he was.
[Amanza laughing]
Well, see, that's the thing, I...
-That's how she got him as a client.
-That's what you call overlap.
[Mary] Yeah.
-That's a strong fucking allegation.
-Yeah.
You'd better have proof
in the fucking pudding
if you're going to make
an accusation like that.
A cheating accusation. Absolutely.
[Amanza] Maybe it's a good thing
I wasn't there.
[laughing] Yeah.
Can we re-enact it, just the three of us?
Like a secret bachelorette party,
just the three of us? [chuckles]
-So I can, like, participate in this fun.
-[Chrishell] Yes.
[Mary] On another night.
-I need to recover first.
-We'll give you a few days.
[all laughing]
♪ Top up, top down, that swagger ♪
♪ Up town, downtown, got that swagger ♪
[engine revving]
[tires screeching]
♪ Up town, downtown, got that swagger ♪
♪ I got the style
She got the style ♪
[Heather] Usually every home
has a broker's open.
So, it's the first time agents and brokers
can come and see a house
before they bring their clients.
We always hope that an agent will walk in
and have a client in mind already,
and bring them back literally the next day
and write an offer before
we even have an open house.
That would be ideal, right? [chuckles]
[Heather] Fuck! I can't walk in heels.
-[Christine] Cute.
-[Davina] I think it's priced well.
Well, it should.
It's in the middle of nowhere-ville.
[both laughing]
-I do not want to grab this cheese. Oops.
-[doorbell rings]
-[Davina] Hello.
-[Heather] Yay!
-[lock rattling]
-[Heather sighs, groans]
[all] Hi!
-[Christine] Hi, babe!
-Welcome to your new home.
[Christine] You and me both
were struggling with the door.
-Look at you.
-Hi, you look great. Mwah!
I'm not gonna close it all the way,
I want people just to walk in.
-This is so fun. Gorgeous.
-Cute, right?
[Davina] I like the skylights.
You guys want food?
I'm just getting everything ready.
Are you expecting a lot of people?
[Heather] Um... Chrishell's coming,
Jason's coming, Brett's coming.
I'm don't know if Mary's coming,
I'm not sure.
-Did you invite her?
-I invited everybody.
Did you guys know Mary had
another bachelorette party?
-Ah!
I didn't know it was a full on...
Were you guys invited?
-No.
-I wasn't.
Hmm. Interesting.
[Christine] I'm starting to think that
the bachelorette party I was invited to
wasn't actually
the real bachelorette party.
[Christine] You know, everyone
from the office was there.
Even Davina was invited.
So, maybe the real bachelorette party
was the one we weren't invited to.
That would kind of hurt my feelings.
Chrishell went, though.
[Christine] I saw that.
I don't know what this second
bachelorette party was.
It's called, "The bachelorette party
we're not invited to."
I mean, let's call a spade a spade.
Did she say bachelorette party
or anything underneath that?
-They were on a stripper pole!
-Yeah.
[Christine] Nicole posted on Instagram,
"Best bachelorette party ever."
[Heather] Wow, really?
I swear to God this was the photo.
[Heather laughing]
[Christine] Coochie out.
You know about the coochie being out.
What can I say?
What!
Brett's here, and Kelsey.
-[Kelsey] Hello.
-[Heather] Hi!
[Brett] Hey, guys. You know Kelsey.
-Hi. How are you doing?
-Hi, I'm Davina. Nice to meet you.
[Heather] Do you want some champagne?
-Yeah, why not.
-Yeah?
-[Heather] How are you feeling?
-[Brett] We got back from Vegas yesterday.
-Romain's bachelor party. Good times.
-Here you go, honey.
-All right, who wants to see the house?
-Let's see it.
[Heather] A little over 2,000 square feet,
four bedrooms, three bathrooms.
Cute little home for a couple
or little family, maybe.
I'm gonna show you guys the master.
-[Christine] Wow!
-[Davina] Nice.
-Pretty.
-[Heather] I love the master bathroom.
[Christine] This is great!
-These bathrooms are so beautiful.
-[Heather] Right, isn't it nice?
It is.
Oh, this is so cute.
-Oh, this is really cute.
-I love this.
It's all one floor, too? I like that.
There's a Jack and Jill bathroom
leading you to the other bedroom.
[Christine] Who's Jack and Jill?
-I'm Jack, you're Jill.
-Love it.
-Unless you wanna, like, flip flop.
-We can switch roles.
-I like that.
-Okay...
[Christine laughing]
[indistinct chatter]
-[Chrishell] I hear them.
-[laughs] Look at that.
Old agents' cards.
[gasps] Let me see that. Who had it?
It doesn't even have a name on here,
how weird.
This guy's name is Coldwell Banker.
[Chrishell chuckles]
-I wanna show you guys the backyard.
-The master's kinda of separate.
Hello! Hi!
[Heather] Hi. Welcome.
[Brett] How are you?
[Heather] Oh, my God, that's so funny.
[all chattering]
-[Christine] Good to see you.
-[cork pops]
-[Jason] Jesus Christ.
-Oh, my gosh, you scared me.
-[doorbell]
-Where'd it go?
-[Davina] Here's some more people, guys.
-Hey, how are you?
-Gorgeous house.
-[Brett] Mwah.
[Jason] Hey, how are you?
Hi, I'm Heather. I'm the listing agent.
Hi, I'm Heather, listing agent.
Here you go, ladies. Take a look at this.
You guys want any champagne?
I just opened a bottle.
[Stephanie] I'm not opposed to champagne.
[Heather] Wonderful.
We also have some snacks over here.
I just gave them the tour.
We're gonna check out the backyard.
-You wanna come back here?
-[Davina] I'm starving too, right?
[Jason] Davina, give me
two seconds with you.
[Davina] Mm-hmm. Yeah.
Please give me good news
on the 75 million dollar listing.
Um, well, I had a showing with an agent
who was previewing for his client.
One showing, you mean?
-Yeah, one showing, but I don't know--
-You have four weeks left.
I don't know if they'll make an offer.
It's a high price, obviously.
It's a ridiculously high price, Davina.
You've had one showing.
Heather's had five showings this week.
It's hard to find qualified people
at that price point.
You pushed me to take this listing
at 75 million dollars.
-That's our reputation.
-I believe in the property.
You are much more optimistic than me,
because I feel--
What am I gonna do, be negative about it?
Take the listing and have a bad attitude?
That's a terrible idea.
A terrible idea, was taking this listing
at 75 million dollars.
We need to get
at least a few more showings.
I'm not saying we have to sell it.
I don't think we're gonna sell it.
We have to make it not look like
we couldn't even get a few showings.
We might sell at the last moment.
We just don't know.
Sometimes the attitude
isn't enough to sell a property.
[Davina] I think Jason is being
unreasonably hard on me.
He's had Hillside for a year
and he's had no action,
so I think he should know better.
-I have to find more qualified people.
-Can you get back to me with a plan.
-In the next four weeks.
-I will.
-All right.
-We'll figure it out.
-[Christine] Whose is this?
-That's a lot.
-Geez, who taught you how to pour?
-[Davina] I know.
I'm surprised we haven't had
an offer on this house yet.
-It's really cute.
-How long has it been on?
-Just a couple of weeks, but still.
-Has there been interest?
I have a client, but he wants to write it
under two. I'm like, "No way."
If it was Mary's listing,
you'd be like, "Yeah."
[Jason] Just to get under her skin?
"I got you a 1.8 offer."
[Jason] We were just talking about you.
-[Chrishell] Hey!
-[Jason] How are you?
-How are you?
-Good to see you, honey.
-[Christine] Are you sick?
-[Heather] What happened to your voice?
[Chrishell] You sound like
a sexy Demi Moore.
-[Mary] All right.
-[girls chuckle]
This is better, actually. At the thing
the other night, I was raspy too.
[Mary] But, um, the following day,
I woke up and I could not speak at all.
Too much partying, girl?
No, uh... too-- [laughs]
Too much of everything.
Too much, too much, uh...
It's just stress.
Too much bachelorette party? You had
a bachelorette party without us I heard.
It was a... No, it was
an impromptu kind of thing.
It was more like people at her house,
so it wasn't really a party. [laughing]
Amanza and I were gonna hang out
at her house 'cause she had the kids...
There were people that weren't invited
that got their feelings hurt.
I'm gonna go...
-You know what? Congrats on your listing.
-Thank you.
-And I'm going to go take a tour.
-[Heather] Okay.
It really was just people
at someone's house.
It wasn't a party at all.
But she text you guys,
she could have text everyone.
I didn't get a text from Mary.
I got a text from Amanza saying
there are people hanging at the house.
But still, no one texted anyone.
-Hey, guys. How are you?
-How are you? Great to see you.
I'm gonna have some people
uninvited to my wedding.
Really fucking fast.
I'm at my wits end right now.
I'm not arguing about anything
with anybody.
-Okay, you don't have to, honey.
-They just started a fight with me.
Maya's feelings were really hurt.
She called me and she was so sad.
She's like, "I'm so confused about Mary.
I thought we were on good terms."
All I know is that
I got a text saying, "Hey, there's some
girls hanging out if you wanna come."
-Right.
-But it was a very coordinated event.
It wasn't just, like, I threw a fucking
salami and fucking bottle of Barefoot,
and let's have some glasses
and call it a night.
It was a coordinated event.
-It was planned.
When have they ever come
to my broker's opens?
Because I actually have listings,
I actually have clients.
-So, how many--
-[Jason] Babe, can you stop?
-This--
-No, I'm not going to stop.
I'm not doing any of this
catty bullshit anymore.
-It's okay, love.
-Come here.
[Mary] I'm done.
Weddings.
This is why you don't get married.
-[Stephanie] I'm eloping.
-Yeah, elope.
[Mary] I swear to God, if they try
to start one more fucking fight with me...
Mary, can you just-- Honey, I hear you.
I'm asking you to take a deep breath.
-I just want you to relax a little bit.
-[Mary sighs]
Oh, God, what are fucking... They're about
to make out right now? Look at this.
Jesus Christ.
Oh, my God, get a room.
I cannot with this.
[Davina] That is so weird, guys.
It's so fucking weird.
[Heather] Can we not do this
at my broker's open, please?
[Davina] That's true.
-Actually, there's people out there.
-[doorbell]
God, these people.
Is Mary seriously crying and having
a breakdown at my broker's open
and Jason is consoling her
with this 10-minute hug?
Like, I don't know
what's going on right now.
I cannot be having other agents, like,
crying at my broker's open.
[Heather] Can we not do this
at my broker's open, please?
I'm happy to leave.
I wasn't the one that started it.
I'm happy to leave, because I came here
taking time out of my actual schedule.
[Heather] I didn't say anything,
so don't blame me.
-I know, I'm not blaming you.
-Can I show you guys something in here?
But I'm not going to fight about anything.
I can't fight about anything else, so...
Yo, you got an agent coming.
[Jason] Heather.
Yeah.
[Christine] Poor Heather.
[Christine] Like, how embarrassing.
There's real estate brokers here.
Heather. How are you?
Thanks for coming.
I don't want there to be...
like, hostility towards me,
for something that...
-I told them that.
-...I didn't plan.
It was just a small thing.
I just told them that, too.
I don't have to invite
every single one of my friends
to every single event.
And she said Maya got her feelings hurt.
Maya was in Miami.
Trying to see what's going on.
I mean, how many times did she
have a get-together and I wasn't invited?
I'm not mad, I don't care.
God! I ate dinner last night
and I didn't even think to invite you!
What?
-God dammit!
-[Chrishell laughing]
I'm a horrible friend.
-[mocking laughter]
-[Brett] Who's that?
[Heather] Christine!
Christine.
We have other agents here.
Oh, my gosh, like, honestly, girls.
Can we just put our stuff aside?
It's highly unprofessional
and it needs to stop.
[Jason] I'm gonna jam.
-Good seeing you, ladies.
-[Heather] Thanks for coming.
Heather, congrats
on a really good showing.
Write that offer, please.
-[Heather] 2.1, okay?
-[Jason] 1.9.
[Heather] Ha!
-He is good at those lowball offers, man.
-[Heather chuckles]
-[Davina] I wish there was fruit.
-[Christine] Do you wanna talk?
-We can help you close up.
-Okay.
[Heather] Yeah?
These shorts are cheap, it's fine.
Um...
I just wanted to clear the air
because the last time
you and I spoke, like, individually,
it was this, you know, blowout thing.
And I don't want it to be like that.
I know your wedding is coming up
and I want us to be on good terms.
Regardless, we used to be so close,
and from things you said--
You're right.
I thought that  we were back to good,
then I found out you were talking
about my relationship to Chrishell.
I wasn't saying anything
negative about it.
I just said what you told me.
I wasn't talking shit,
I wasn't saying anything bad.
I was like, "I don't know."
It didn't sound like the conversation
was "I don't know" though.
It sounded like there was
a solid point of view.
[Mary] I'm telling you what was said,
about, like, your relationship,
how did you guys meet, it was so fast...
I'm like, "I don't know.
This is what she told me."
But if you were my actual friend,
it shouldn't have been, like, questions.
-I didn't-- I didn't have questions.
-Like, "She was my friend and--"
They were saying, what do I know?
You know what?
I used to always think if you had
something to say, just tell me.
You know what? Y'all just talk
behind my back, I don't care.
If we were friends why wasn't I invited
to the bachelorette party
that you just had? The second one.
[Mary] That wasn't a bachelorette party.
That was a get-together
at Amanza's house with my sister.
[Mary] It was an impromptu thing.
I'll be honest,
Maya was really hurt she wasn't invited.
Maya was at my bachelorette party
with all of you guys.
All of you guys were at
my bachelorette party.
And I thought everyone
had a very good time.
I had a great time.
So if I want to hang out with my sister,
doesn't meant I have to invite
the rest of the freaking world.
So I don't know why Maya is concerned.
Maya's pregnant, she can't do shit anyway.
I mean, it was a coordinated thing.
There was, like,  a pole...
Amanza did that the day of.
-She did it the day of.
-She could have texted people the day of.
Christine, I'm not gonna fight about this.
I'm just saying, call a spade a spade.
Christine, you're being very immature.
I don't think I am,
I'm actually being very mature.
I invited you to my bachelorette party.
So if I'm not allowed to hang out
with my sister and my best friend
-without inviting all my...
-That's not what I'm saying.
-...coworkers.
-You should've included others
-if you're gonna put it on Instagram.
-I did not. I didn't put anything, did I?
[Christine]
I think you're missing the point.
No, you're missing the point.
[Mary] I'm not going to play
childish games.
I'm not going to have to justify.
I'm glad you came
to my bachelorette party.
I'm glad you were invited. It was lovely
having you at my bachelorette party.
Whagt I've done-- If I have had dinner
with someone since then,
I'm sorry you weren't invited
to me and Romain's dinner.
I'm sorry if you weren't invited
to my sister and I hanging out,
-having a drink together. I'm sorry.
-That's not what this is about.
That's exactly what this is about,
because you're upset
because you weren't invited
to a small impromptu--
-It didn't look small or impromptu.
-You weren't there so you wouldn't know.
But Chrishell got invited.
The stuff you say just
literally doesn't make sense.
I think it's interesting for Christine
to come in and make a big scene.
This is really an inappropriate place
to do this or to act like that,
but, you know...
when is Christine appropriate?
I don't know.
Okay, well I'm going to lose
my voice even more,
so I'm gonna take off because I have
some wedding planning to do.
Sometimes you have things
-and you don't invite everybody to them.
-You were there.
You can't say this was
a short get-together.
Chrishell, bitch lives in the Valley.
It'd take her 45 minutes to get there
if she doesn't hit traffic.
Don't say this was
a last minute get-together.
She had to plan it.
She had to Waze her way there.
Just saying.
Have a good night.
-[Heather] Bye.
-Bye.
How did your conversation go?
I mean, she can't... have a conversation.
She just... [mock stammers]
And talks in circles.
"Well, my sister was in town
and this and that and..."
She doesn't like confrontation.
She's just had it--
It's not confrontation.
It's just being a fucking adult
and expressing your feelings.
She always blames it on someone else.
It's always, "Oh, no, that was Romain,
and that was this..."
[Heather] I'm trying to look
at everyone's point of view.
-I do underst--
-Stop. Heather.
Stop being a little bitch right now.
-[Chrishell sighs]
-Stop being a little bitch.
Mary is not a bad person, I don't think
anyone here is a bad person.
-No, I'm not saying that.
-People had feelings hurt.
So let's just all take a step backwards...
-She was very defensive.
-She's very defensive.
She's very deflective,
and she never talks straight.
When you don't talk straight,
it makes you look like a fucking idiot.
Well, she's not a fucking idiot.
I'm not saying she's a fucking idiot,
it makes you look--
But we know that she's not.
-But I said it makes you look like one.
-I heard what you said, but she's not.
♪ Yeah! I won't give
I won't give up on me ♪
♪ I won't give
-Should I try it on?
-Give me those.
Yeah, go. Go, go, go.
-[Sabrina] Let's try.
-Let's do it.
[Sabrina] Ooh-ooh! Almost there.
[Mary] Your work is almost done.
[Sabrina] Perfect.
[Sabrina and Mary chatting indistinctly]
I feel like I should be in
a Michael Jackson video.
[Mary] Hey, Amanza?
Christine's texting me.
She wants to talk.
Okay... [chuckles]
[Mary] I told her I'm trying
to do the dress fitting,
so she might be stopping by
to talk about last night.
So she wants to come
to your dress fitting?
[Mary] I don't want any drama.
This whole thing is so stupid.
-Does it-- Does it look good?
-Oh, yeah.
You look absolutely stunning.
Yay!
It fits you like a glove.
It's so beautiful.
So she text me. She says
that she wants to, like,
make things better
-before the wedding, which I'd love.
-Oh, my God.
[Amanza] That is so stupid.
It was pure stripper pole fun.
[Mary] Thank you, Amanza. Thank you.
-[Amanza] I found my new side hustle.
-I want a stripper pole.
I know, right? If real estate
doesn't work out for me...
A little extra walking around money.
[cell phone vibrating]
Christine's here.
I'm gonna, um-- I'm gonna go get her.
-I'll be right back.
-You got your boxing gloves on?
[laughs] I don't need them, honey.
[Christine] Hey, Amanza!
[Amanza] Did you bring me flowers?
[Christine] These are for Mary, actually.
Are those real flowers
or are they clown flowers
that you're gonna squirt water
in her face?
What? No! Why would you say that?
I came here to talk to her and apologize.
I want her to have the best
for her wedding. That's why I'm here.
Best movie ever, Kevin Costner,
Whitney Houston, Bodyguard.
And I'm getting major vibes of it
because Amanza has become
Mary's bodyguard.
It's like, no one can have a conversation
with her or talk to her
without her butting in
or getting in the way.
She doesn't have to be worried.
I'm here to apologize.
I have flowers in my hand.
I'm not gonna punch her in the face.
I don't feel good about the way that,
you know, last night happened,
and I just want to make sure that
her and I clear the air of everything,
and apologize.
Okay.
[Amanza] Whatever you say better be nice
because she's at her breaking point.
No drama, I promise.
I'll give you guys a minute.
Thanks.
[Christine gasps] Hi, babe!
-Hey, how are you?
-[Christine] You look beautiful.
Thank you.
-I brought you flowers.
-Oh, thank you.
I know this is a weird time
because you're really busy,
but I did want to come here
and apologize because I know
things got a little
out of hand last night.
I want to apologize if I brought
everything up at the wrong time
and I want to apologize
for being a total bitch.
Thank you.
Forgive me if I hurt your feelings
in any way.
What I realized last night
after I got home was that...
"Wow, Mary and I actually
haven't talked in so long."
I haven't talked to you
since our fight at my listing.
And it's been really hard
that I had to go the office
where you and Chrishell
are talking about your dress fitting,
and all these things
that I'm not getting invited to,
so I'm feeling isolated.
I lost my friend and I don't know why.
There was no intention of ever trying
to hurt anybody's feelings.
I've been busy with work and the wedding.
You've been off traveling.
Before, you were like, "No, we're cool."
So, when something happens,
I'm like, "Okay, maybe we're not cool?"
So when it comes to me and you,
I agree that we do need to talk,
but right now I'm days away
from my wedding.
And I want my old friend back.
-We should've just had a conversation.
-Right.
[Mary] Please come to me.
I don't want fights.
I don't want constant,
"Did you hear this?
Do you know what she said?"
I feel stupid for that.
Yeah.
[Christine] From now on...
let's just...
try to get back to where we were.
We will.
I think Christine is genuine
in her apology, but...
I don't know. [sighs]
I mean, things have gone
up and down before,
but I think she is and I hope she is
because I miss my old girl.
I want you to have
the most amazing wedding.
[Mary] Yeah.
A no-drama wedding.
♪ Oh-oh
Woah-oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ I just wanna dive into the blue ♪
♪ It doesn't really matter what we do ♪
♪ Don't let the moment pass us by ♪
♪ Just trust that the universe is right ♪
-Come here.
-Uh, thank you.
-You doing okay?
-I'm good, I'm good.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
-[Mary] You got it?
-[Anna] I got it.
-Uh-oh. I got the bag dirty.
-Yes.
-[Mary] I'm here.
-Yay!
-[Anna] Are you excited?
-Oh, my goodness. I am.
Yay!
-I'm, like, nervous a little bit.
-[all laughing]
-A little bit.
-[Nicole] Mary?
-Yeah.
-Have you done your showing yet?
No, not yet.
I cannot believe you're doing that today,
you crazy lady.
You're a trooper, I'll give you that.
So I get a call from Preston,
another agent.
And he wants to see
my Doheny listing today,
which happens to be my wedding venue.
I was like, "There's a wedding,
there's stuff set up every place."
-You didn't tell him it was yours?
-No. No, um...
Not exactly convenient timing,
but I'm going to do it.
I'm going to be there anyway, so...
I can't let this wedding get
in the way of work. [chuckles]
I said it'd be better if you come,
like, tomorrow or Monday
when things are taken down
and it'll probably show better.
He said he's only in town today.
-It's a big music producer...
-Okay.
...and he really wants to see it, so...
Well, the house shows well no matter what.
I'm gonna be here so let's do it.
If I sell it on my wedding day, boom.
That'd be pretty cool.
-[Mary sighs]
-[Nicole] Is Amanza still not here yet?
I guess not.
[Mary] To be fair,
she's got two kids in tow.
[Nicole] Are you enjoying the day?
Chilling?
I'm a little, like, shaky, I think, but...
[Nicole] Remember we're all here for you,
so timeline just doesn't matter.
-Just relax.
-[Anna] Yeah.
[Mary] Okay, guys,
I'm gonna go put that robe on.
-[Amanza] I'm here!
-This, um, is the vows.
-[Mary] I need a drink.
-[Nicole] I got you.
-[champagne cork pops]
-Oh, look at your robe. So cute.
-Hi.
-Hi, hon. How are you?
Good. How are you?
[Mary] I really am getting
a little, like...
[inhales deeply, exhales]
Oh, my God.
-[Mary] I'm, like... stressing.
-Mary?
[Amanza] Gotta break it a little
cause it's big.
[knocking on door]
-What...
-[Mary] Hi. Preston?
-Hey, how's it going?
-[Mary] Hi!
-How are you?
-Oh, my God, are you getting married?
[Mary laughing] I am!
-Congratulations.
-[Mary] Thank you.
[Amanza] Only Mary.
This is the hardest working chick, like...
It's your wedding day for the love of God.
[Mary] I know,
but I'm here anyway,
so take a look around and then
I'll run down there and meet you.
-Okay?
-[Preston] Thank you. So sorry.
No, don't be sorry.
[Mary] How close are we
to a stopping point?
I can just clip it here
while you show them.
[Mary] Okay.
Okay. I'm going to go show him
this property really fast.
[Mary] Hi! Sorry. Okay.
So, yeah, it's a bit of a mess,
-but I hope you see through everything.
-[Preston] This is awesome.
All of this is Waterworks.
La Cornue stove.
-[Preston] Really nice.
-I know.
-Isn't that stove incredible? Right?
-[cook] It's amazing.
Okay, so, here is the formal living room.
-The fireplace is imported from Italy.
-[Preston] That's cool.
-Yeah, it is cool and the family room.
-Wow.
French doors open up to the backyard.
[Mary] The master bedroom is just amazing.
All bedrooms have en-suite baths.
The backyard is the selling point
of the house.
[Preston] Gorgeous!
-Yeah.
-So nice.
The pool is amazing. This guest house
over here has a kitchenette.
Bathroom, shower...
It's a studio, basically.
Complete privacy.
-[Preston] Amazing for a wedding too.
-[Mary] I know, I know.
-Thank you again so much for showing me.
-Oh, my pleasure.
-And we need to make the sale.
-[laughing] I know.
I know, I plan to.
This would be epic if I actually sell
my wedding venue on my wedding day.
Love it.
[Jason] Where's Romain, let's go, bud.
-It's your wedding.
-I know.
You sure you wanna go through this, bud?
To the last moment of being single, man.
Been nice knowing you.
-Does this look good?
-[Brett] Yeah, that's right.
-Do you want the collar outside the vest?
-No, inside. God, you guys.
Brett, you've clearly
never modeled before.
[Maya] Wow, this is beautiful.
-I'm gonna fall. Can I have your arm?
-I know.
[Jason] VIP couple.
Hi, guys.
-Hi, how are you?
-Hey, love.
[Jason] Mwah.
-[all] Cheers.
-Cheers to the bride and groom.
[Christine] Give me a hug. Hi, honey!
Hi, I'm Chrishell.
[Mary] You guys look so nice.
All of you guys look amazing.
-[Steve] Not as nice as you.
-[Mary] Oh... Aw.
You guys ready?
-[Theresa] Yes.
-Yeah. We got this.
-[Christine] Is this us?
-Yeah.
I'm a little tipsy already.
-[Maya] Are you?
-[Heather chuckles]
Oh, you want it in the front? Sorry.
-You want it in front?
-What?
Your ponytail, I was gonna put it back.
-I'm good, thanks.
-[Christine] I was fixing your hair!
[laughing] Leave my hair alone.
-No, I was fixing it.
-I'm gonna sit like this.
[Chrishell] Oh, here they come.
I love weddings.
♪ They say ♪
♪ Your heart speeds up ♪
♪ And the world slows down ♪
[Maya] That's Romain's Dad.
Is that Mary's mom?
♪ They say that you know ♪
♪ Beyond a shadow of a doubt ♪
♪ When you finally find ♪
♪ The one ♪
[cheering, clapping]
[Heather] I'm gonna cry.
[Mary inhales deeply, sighs]
♪ They say that you feel ♪
♪ How I feel right now ♪
♪ When you finally find ♪
♪ The one ♪
[Mary laughing]
♪ And I've finally found the one ♪
[Mary chuckling] Oh.
[Nicole] Today is a celebration
of love, commitment,
friendship, and family,
but, most importantly,
of two people who are in it forever.
The two of you met and fell in love
by chance.
But you're here today
because you're making a choice.
You both are choosing each other.
Beside the fact that these two
look like a walking Calvin Klein ad...
[all laughing]
...the beauty of their union
is even greater on the inside.
I think everyone here today
will agree with me,
you both have chosen very wisely.
Without further ado,
let's get these lovebirds married.
Now, I have a very serious question
to ask both of you.
Romain, do you take Mary to be
your lawfully wedded wife...
I do.
-Oh!
-[Mary laughing]
[Nicole] Hold on,
it's not quite that easy.
...to love and cherish
from this day forward,
for better or for worse,
for richer or for poorer,
in sickness and in health?
-I still do.
-[Nicole] Okay, good.
-[all laughing]
-[Nicole] Good.
And Mary, do you take Romain
to be your lawfully wedded husband,
to love and cherish from this day forward,
for better or for worse,
for richer or for poorer,
in sickness and in health?
I do.
-Mary and Romain, please join hands.
-[Mary sniffles]
[Nicole] Romain, please repeat after me.
"I, Romain, take you, Mary."
I, Romain, take you, Mary.
"To be my wife."
To be my wife.
"To love you when you drive me crazy."
To love you when you drive me crazy.
[chuckles]
"And to always remember
how grateful I am..."
And to always remember
how grateful I am...
"...to have you by my side."
...to have you by my side.
Okay.
-Got my page back here.
-[Mary sniffles] Oh, here we go.
Good?
[Nicole] All right, Mary, repeat after me.
"I, Mary, take you, Romain."
[repeating vows in French]
"To be my husband."
[Mary speaking French]
"To love you when you drive me crazy."
"And to always remember
how grateful I am..."
[Mary speaking French]
"To have you by my side."
[speaking French]
-[applause]
-[Mary chuckles]
-[Nicole] Good job, babe.
-[cheering]
-[Nicole] May I please have the rings?
-[dogs barking]
-Come, babies.
-Come here, babies!
[Mary] Aw, Nico.
Nico.
-[Nicole] By the authority vested in me...
-[laughter]
...by the beautiful state of California,
it is my joyful responsibility
to officially pronounce you
as husband...
and wife.
You may now French kiss your bride.
-[all laughing]
-[Christine] Yay!
[cheering, applause]
[Nicole] Ladies and gentlemen,
it is my privilege to present to you
for the very first time,
Mr. and Mrs. Mary Fitzgerald
and Romain Bonnet.
[all laughing]
[applause]
[cheering]
Thank you.
My baby...
[Mary chuckles]
[Mary] I love Romain more than anything.
I couldn't be happier
with how the wedding turned out.
It was everything
I could have ever hoped for.
-[Jason] Can we get a--
-[Amanza] Group hug.
[Amanza] I love my besties.
-[Chrishell] Oh, this is beautiful.
-So beautiful!
-Should we get a drink before we sit?
-Yes, let's do it.
[Chrishell] Thank you so much.
Do you have straws by chance?
No, it's okay. Save the turtles, cheers.
[Maya] Wait, guys,
is it self-serve, maybe...
[Heather] Cheers!
-Cheers!
-[Heather] I need water, though.
-I haven't had any water.
-No!
You don't need water.
It's a wedding. Cheers!
Okay, fine. Fine, let's do it.
Yeah, rub it in my face,
rub it in my face that I cannot drink.
Aww, I miss him!
Miss you.
Baby, you are so sexy
and I miss you so much.
Your girl looks pretty hot, too.
I love you.
[Maya] I don't do it either.
We miss you, Tarek! [laughs]
[Christine] You guys are cute.
Chrishell, what are you doing
on your Sunday off?
Um...
Anything fun?
Justin and I are going...
We like to go have a few drinks,
then we like to go drunk shopping.
I love it.
It's a dumb thing, but we...
[Maya] It's not, it's super cute.
It's fun.
It's like a silly fun thing we...
By the way, I'm sorry
I missed your broker's open.
-[Heather] It's okay. I forgive you.
-Thank you.
-How was it?
-Stressful.
-[laughter]
-[Maya] Really?
Wait, what?
-The broker's open.
-My broker's open.
[Maya] Why? Was it not busy or--?
[Heather laughing]
Why are we looking at Christine?
-[Heather] Because...
-What did you do?
-Huh.
-What did she not do? [laughing]
[Maya] What happened?
Mary and Christine had a little moment.
We were talking about how she had
a second bachelorette party.
-She brought that up--
-[Christine] I mentioned it.
I said, Heather and Maya
really had their feelings hurt.
-I was a little bit offended too.
-I was gonna ask, how'd you feel?
It wasn't a second
bachelorette party, though.
It wasn't.
Amanza had some people at her house,
we literally, like, Postmated dinner.
It wasn't, like, a party.
And it certainly wasn't
a bachelorette party.
Do you see what's going on right here?
[Mary] It looks like they're starting
drama, right? I swear to God...
-Yeah! Don't worry about it.
-Amanza...
-Hey, Amanza.
-[Amanza] I got this.
[Christine] Chrishell told me,
Amanza actually planned it.
Like, Mary didn't plan it.
-Oh, okay. That makes more sense.
-[Chrishell] I get it.
Everyone has their own things
and their own feelings,
-but when someone's getting married--
-Hey, guys!
What's happening?
-Hey, we just talked about you.
-Does someone need an olive branch?
We just talked about you.
Good, I felt it. I have psych--
I felt it, I was like,
"Somebody needs an olive branch."
Yeah, we were just talking
about the broker's open.
-We talked about...
-You're like...
...you not inviting us
to the bachelorette party. [laughing]
I mean, we were out of town, granted,
but it would just be nice to get a text.
We can talk about that...
not at Mary's wedding.
-Happy to address it, but not tonight.
-[Maya] That's very true.
[Jason] Amanza's shaking them out.
They're all smiling.
[Amanza] I look over,
it looked like there was
something going on,
-so then I just decided to come down.
-[Heather] There was nothing going on.
[Maya] No, we're actually good.
-We're actually having good conversation.
-Good conversation, yeah.
All positive.
Christine, are you okay? You don't look...
[Christine] No, I'm great.
-I don't hold grudges.
-[Christian laughing]
Okay, I'm going to go continue
drinking my wine.
Enjoy, Amanza. Drink one for me
'cause I can't drink.
[Christine] Um...
Awkward Amanza.
[laughter]
[Amanza] Excuse me.
There was some drama.
It's a jungle.
She's like the weird creepy uncle
that pops out of the fucking bushes.
I was like, "Oh!" [laughing]
-Nothing was happening.
-We were just having a conversation.
We weren't like, "Ra-ra-ra!"
[Christine] Fucking bodyguard with her,
"Huh-huh-huh!"
-Linebacking her ass.
-Who?
Who do you think? Awkward Amanza!
-Oh, Amanza. For Mary?
-She's got her bodyguard, Jesus Christ!
I have been on the receiving end
of Christine's wrath
and that's really why
I've steered clear of her recently.
-They've known each other for 15 years.
-I understand,
but I just want to have a conversation.
She's like, linebacker. I'm just like,
"Let me have a conversation
with someone, please."
Never would I do that shit.
[Chrishell] It looks like
she has a new target,
which is Amanza.
[glasses clinking]
[Chrishell] You can make it strong
if you want.
♪ Gonna pump the party up, y'all! ♪
Now I'm gonna start to have
some fucking fun.
Ha!
[camera shutter clicking]
[Amanza] Cheers.
With my imaginary drink.
So good!
-I think it's all going really well.
-I think so, too.
I came... I literally, like...
I thought you guys were having a heated,
dramatic moment when I came over.
Yeah, it was such a surprise,
you showed up...
[Amanza] No, because it looked like...
something might be going on, I don't know.
Yeah.
They were upset, obviously,
that they weren't invited...
No, I wouldn't say upset.
You know, we saw Nicole's photos
on Instagram
and I'm like, "Wait a minute!"
We didn't know about it.
We just felt a bit not included,
but that's okay.
-Obviously...
-Well, I invited who I wanted to invite.
Basically, nobody there
had ever started drama with Mary.
Not everybody needs
to be invited to everything.
I don't think you have
to explain yourself.
The girls were confused thinking it was
a bachelorette party, but it wasn't.
-We were gonna hang out.
-It wasn't.
That's where the confusion happened.
You know Christine being so upset...
Clearly, Christine and Mary still have
stuff they need to talk about.
Christine, you know,
she's very impulsive at times.
At least, let's say, when she messes up,
she owns it.
She's like, "Look, sorry about that."
And she apologizes.
-[Maya] Chrishell?
-No, she doesn't.
-She apologized to you.
-She apologized to Mary.
How many times are you supposed to accept
someone's "sorry"
and then they do
the same thing over again?
She lashes out,
and then later be like, "Sorry, girl,"
and then think everything
is supposed to be fine.
[Christine] There's some shit
going on over there.
[Heather] Okay.
-Should we go over there?
-No.
I'm glad those bitches
are so obsessed with us.
-[Heather laughing]
-But to pop off on Mary.
-Who did, Christine?
-Somebody called Mary a jerk...
Uh, she called her more than that.
What did she say about Mary?
So Mary left and she comes in the room,
and she's like,
"She's acting like a fucking idiot.
I can't even talk to her."
And I was like,
"Okay, well, she's not a fucking idiot."
[Mary] Where's Romain?
-Hi.
-Oh, am I interrupting something?
-[Amanza] Yeah.
-[Maya chuckling]
-This is your day,
you can do whatever you want.
-[all laughing]
-I feel like you know with--
Hold on, so she said what about Mary?
She said she was acting
like a fucking idiot.
And she was very adamant about this.
She said it several times.
So I told her,
"First of all, no she's not."
She was like, "I didn't say she was,
I said she was acting like one."
I said, "I heard what you said,
and we all know she's not."
And she goes off
and, like, she starts mimicking her,
being like... "Oh, oh, oh."
Trying to act like her,
You know how she does
and Mary wasn't doing any of that,
but she was hot,
and she was just trashing Mary, so...
[Christine chuckling]
-And this one!
-Swing dancing.
[both laughing]
So, are you going to say
anything to Christine, or...?
[Christine screaming, laughing]
[both laughing]
Oh, my God!
I'm not going to say anything tonight
'cause it's Mary's wedding...
but I will.
♪ It seems like
We're headed for a showdown ♪
Christine always talks about being loyal,
loyalty to friends...
I'll show you loyalty.
[cheering]
♪ Baby, karma is gonna get you ♪
♪ Karma is gonna get you ♪
[cheering]
♪ Watch out ♪
♪ You'll get what is coming ♪
♪ You know the song ♪
♪ So hit the ground running ♪
♪ Karma is gonna get you ♪
I just closed
on the 44 million dollar house.
-[all screaming] What?
-[bell ringing loudly]
I build the houses, you sell the houses.
Maybe this property is over your league.
So I was thinking maybe
you could get involved.
What do you think
you can you bring to the table?
-Bitches, watch out.
-[Davina chuckles]
[Jason] Hey, I have something for you.
Is Jason giving Mary another listing?
What about us?
I don't like being around
egotistic males.
-Would you guys ever...
-Consider leaving?
-I'm just telling you.
-I'm just telling you!
We are never gonna sell that listing
and we are walking away from that house.
Who calls their friend a fucking idiot?
I can call her whatever I want.
You can't call me whatever you want
and expect to be friends.
I feel like she's trying drive a wedge
between me and you.
[Romain] I never wanted to hide anything,
but it's wrong what I've done.
Wait, guys... Guys, guys, guys...
-What is it?
-It's all over the internet right now.
[announcer] Chrishell Stause
is dealing with change.
Her husband, This is Us star
Justin Hartley, filed for divorce.
[Chrishell]
I'm just kind of in shock with it all.
He just blindsided you?
It's just a lot all at once because the
whole world knows... I love him so much.
This was my best friend.
Who do I talk to now?
-She knows why this happened.
-Of course, yeah.
Think you're gonna go
to Christine's wedding?
[sighs]
[Chrishell]
I don't want to be here right now.
I don't want to do this anymore.
That's fucked up.
♪ I can see everything now ♪
♪ The lights shining over the crowd ♪
♪ The new world changing ♪
♪ I can see it ♪